Email: victor.catamo.rojas@gmail.com Mobile: +420 725 913 045

Description

Software Engineer with a Bachelor's degree in Informatics Engineering with around 6 years of experience developing software. My area of expertise is Web Application Development, working as a Fullstack Developer. I am comfortable using C#, .NET Framework, .NET Core, JavaScript and have experience in Frontend technologies like Vue and Angular. I also use tools like Docker Compose, TravisCI and Jenkins in my development workflow.

Skillset

Current Stack: .NET Core, VueProgramming Languages: C#, JavaScript, PythonDatabases: SQL Server, MongoDBSpoken Languages: English (C1), Spanish (Native)

Experience

Techona *Frontend Software Engineer*

Prague, Czech Republic *May 2019 - December 2019*

- Casino games development, using an internal JavaScript framework that wrapped Pixi JS and used the Google Closure Library to enable modularity
- Participated in creating a new iteration of a game with a new theme, assets, and new behaviors
- Reduced the creation time of a new Projects in Jira from days to minutes, by making an Excel add-in that managed bulk creations and updates, while considering task hierarchy. It was coded using VSTO with C# and integrated with Jira REST API

The App Master

Senior Software Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina July 2018 - August 2019

- Senior Developer in a reengineering for the platform of one of the main online theater ticket sellers in Argentina
- As part of a 2 developers team, I worked and took decision in all the stages of the project. The solution consisted of a Back Office application made using JQuery and ASP.NET MVC, a REST API made using .NET Core, and a client for the ticket sellers/call center was made using Vue
- Improved release times by 90%, compared to the old FTP release process, by implementing CI/CD with Jenkins

Hexacta Mid-Level Software Developer

Buenos Aires, Argentina July 2017 - July 2018

- Worked developing internal tools for an US company specialized in risk management solutions for multiple industries
- Managed improved Production Environments Performance by an average of 20%, replacing cross-applies and cursors with more efficient alternatives, in an ASP.NET WebForms project that handled most of the logic in SQL Stored Procedures

• Was responsible of the Frontend of a new project made with ASP.NET Core MVC, Entity Framework Core, JQuery, Kendo UI and TypeScript, which was hosted on Azure

Freelancer *Mid-Level Software Developer*

Remote, Venezuela January 2017 - July 2017

- Created a proof of concept of Microsoft Bot Framework for SiderysBSN that integrated with Outlook and guided the user to set up meetings from Skype
- Implemented Twillio video calls between Mobile and Web for a startup named HLink iFarmacias. The solution was made using ASP.NET MVC and JQuery

GIGA I.T. *Mid-Level Software Developer*

Remote, Venezuela June 2016 - May 2017

- Developed a new module to dynamically handle bulk loads to the database from spreadsheets with different layouts. Implemented it using ASP.NET MVC and OpenXML, using Hangfire handle the longer processes in the background.
- Worked in bug fixing and implementing new modules for multiple ASP.NET MVC projects.

Norkut *Entry-Level Software Developer*

Nueva Esparta, Venezuela February 2015 - June 2016

- Implemented, as a proof of concept, a new client in **Angular.js 1.x** for an existing ASP.NET MVC project. Fully functional in under a week
- Reduced by 50% the release time of a module for Silverlight application, by adding libraries "hot-swapping" support

Norkut *Software Development Intern*

Nueva Esparta, Venezuela April 2014 - November 2014

Side Projects

Sorting Algorithms Visualizer Vue, Vuex, Vuetify

https://catamo.github.io/sorting-visualizer
A mobile first sorting algorithms visualizer, coded using Vue.js

Venue Hotel Finder MVP Vue, Nuxt, TailwindCSS <u>Download from Google Drive</u>

MVP for a hotel finder for event venues. Complete with a mock server

Angular Dart Bookmarks

AngularDart, AngularDart Components

https://github.com/Catamo/angular dart bookmarks
Follow along of a tutorial on AngularDart, which I plan to improve

Education

Universidad de Margarita

Porlamar, Venezuela

Ingeniero de Sistemas (Bachelor of Informatics Engineering)

2010 - 2015

Multidisciplinary degree that combines engineering with informatics. In one hand it has courses like Calculus, Physics and Operations Research. On the other hand, the students learn about Programming, Data Structures, Databases and Computer Architecture.